BHOGADI LOKESH () Featured

Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Engineering, Software

Development, Application Support, Project Management, Change Management, Incident

Management, Configuration Management, Requirement

Gathering, Troubleshooting, BMC Remedy, SQL Server, Linux



Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 2 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Pune, Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer/Developer, Software Engineering, Software Development, Application Support, Project

Management, Change Management, Incident Management, Configuration Management, Requirement

Gathering, Troubleshooting, BMC Remedy, SQL Server, Linux

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Possess 3+ years of experience in Information Technology and Application Support.

Working as Application Analyst and supporting multiple Applications in Enterprise Contact Center Space.

Verification of the application logs and analyzing the system issues, and escalate.

Maintaining core application components (including Genesys Database, CTI, IVR, servers) stability - restarts etc.

Monitoring, Analyze and resolve failures of the Genesys Applications.

Performing daily NICE Validations and troubleshooting the NICE voice and screen logger's issues

Working on Genesys and Nuance IVR support from Middleware and Integration perspective.

To be associated with an organization that gives me scope to update my knowledge and in accordance with latest trends in IT Industry and be a part of a team that dynamically works towards the growth of organization.

Work Experience

VFISLK GLOBAL SERVICES Pvt Ltd as Software Engineer

May 2020 to Nov 2020

Worked as Admin for providing Inbound Access and Adding agents to Ccpulse groups and Reporting to the Middleware team for the IVR Function verification.

Performing Genesys Health checks and troubleshooting

Maintaining the different contact centre applications that different Business use for the day to day.

The contact center specialist is responsible for analyzing, planning, designing and developing applications

Worked on the GAX ,GA, WRAPPER,SOAP UI,Speech Storm

Developing the IVR call flow

Support business requests for routing changes using the necessary process controls to ensure production operation is not risk

Support periodic platform upgrades and /or solution design changes that may arise.

Infobase Systems as Software Engineer

Sep 2017 to Feb 2020

Genesys support

Client: Unisys India Pvt Ltd Project : Cardinal Health

Role: - Genesys Support Engineer

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=3e6a52c67c853f860d6a11e23b239b035c0e0c561b140d16061940095b...

Platform Used: - Genesys SCI and SCME, CCPulse+, BMC Remedy, Genesys Agent Workspace Desktop Edition Team Size: - 8

Roles and Responsibilities:-

Maintaining the different contact centre applications that different Business use for the day to day. Health Checks of the Genesys, Nice applications on daily basis.

Monitoring for the different Contact centre applications for sound health of the applications and Server.

Responding to the Service Requests created by the customers in response for technical support delivered within SLA

Worked on the Genesys Framework, SCI, CME, Genesys URS, Tserver, Start servers

Working on the Agent Softphone issues and escalating them based on the issue.

Working on Agent Real-time Reports on CCPulse+.

Worked on the Genesys CTI servers patching for both Windows and UNIX servers.

Performing the Agent additions and patching support for the Genesys Servers.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Malla Reddy Institute of Engineering and Technology, Hyderabad in 2017

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Windows Server, Linux, T-servers	
Microsoft SQL Server, BMC Remedy Tool	
GAX,soap UI	
Genesys Framework	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

Projects

Project Title: Retirement Services

Client: voya financial

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: May 2020 - Nov 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Project Details: Worked as Admin for providing Inbound Access and Adding agents to Ccpulse groups and Reporting to the Middleware team for the IVR Function verification.

Performing Genesys Health checks and troubleshooting

Maintaining the different contact centre applications that different Business use for the day to day.

The contact center specialist is responsible for analyzing, planning, designing and developing applications

Worked on the GAX ,GA, WRAPPER,SOAP UI,Speech Storm

Developing the IVR call flow

Support business requests for routing changes using the necessary process controls to ensure production operation is not risk

Support periodic platform upgrades and /or solution design changes that may arise.

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=3e6a52c67c853f860d6a11e23b239b035c0e0c561b140d16061940095b...

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time